<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Caserta Tour</string>

    <string name="monuments_fragment">Monuments</string>
    <string name="restaurants_fragment">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="hotels_fragment">Hotels</string>
    <string name="shopping_fragment">Shopping</string>

    <string name="royal_palace_description">The Royal Palace of Caserta (Italian: Reggia di Caserta; Neapolitan: Reggia \'e Caserta)
        is a former royal residence in Caserta, southern Italy, constructed for the Bourbon kings of Naples. It is one of the largest palaces erected in Europe
        during the 18th century. In 1997, the palace was designated a UNESCO World Heritage Site; its nomination described it as "the swan song of the spectacular
        art of the Baroque, from which it adopted all the features needed to create the illusions of multidirectional space".[1] In terms of volume,
        the Royal Palace of Caserta is the largest royal residence in the world[2] with over 2 million m³[3] and covering an area of about 235,000 m². \n
        \n
    History\n
        \n
        The construction of the palace was begun in 1752 for Charles VII of Naples, who worked closely with his architect, Luigi Vanvitelli.
        When Charles saw Vanvitelli\'s grandly scaled model for Caserta, it filled him with emotion "fit to tear his heart from his breast".
        In the end, he never slept a night at the Reggia, as he abdicated in 1759 to become King of Spain, and the project was carried to only partial completion
        for his third son and successor, Ferdinand IV of Naples.
        The political and social model for Vanvitelli\'s palace was Versailles, which, though strikingly different in its variety and disposition, solves similar problems of
        assembling and providing for king, court and government in a massive building with the social structure of a small city, confronting a baroque view of a highly
        subordinated nature, la nature forcée. The population of Caserta Vecchia was moved 10 kilometers to provide a work force closer to the palace.
        A silk manufactory at San Leucio resort was disguised as a pavilion in the immense parkland.
        Another of the king\'s primary objects was to have a magnificent new royal court and administrative center for the kingdom in a location protected from sea attack.
        and distant from the revolt-prone and congested city of Naples. To provide the king with suitable protection, troop barracks were housed within the palace.

        The Royal Palace of Madrid, where Charles had grown up, which had been devised by Filippo Juvarra for Charles\' father, Philip V of Spain, and Charlottenburg Palace
        provided models. A spacious octagonal vestibule seems to have been inspired by Basilica di Santa Maria della Salute in Venice, while the palatine chapel is
        most often compared to the Royal Chapel at Versailles. Vanvitelli died in 1773: the construction was continued by his son Carlo and then by other architects;
        but the elder Vanvitelli\'s original project, which included a vast pair of frontal wings similar to Bernini\'s wings at St. Peter\'s, was never finished. \n
        Source Wikipedia.\n
        Official website:
    </string>
    <string name="royal_palace_website">http://www.reggiadicaserta.beniculturali.it/</string>

    <string name="san_leucio_description">San Leucio is a frazione of the comune of Caserta, in the region of Campania in southern Italy.
        It is most notable for a resort developed around an old silk factory, included in the UNESCO World Heritage sites list in 1997.\n
         \n
    History\n
        \n
        In 1750 Charles VII of Naples, advised by minister Bernardo Tanucci, selected this place, originally the site of a royal hunting lodge for the Acquaviva family
        (now restored, and known as Palazzo del Belvedere), for an unusual social and technological experiment, a different model of production based on technical
        innovation and alert to the needs of workers. In its early days, San Leucio resort was a place for pleasure and a royal hunting preserve,
        built on the ruins of Saint Leucio church, where an aqueduct carried water to the waterfalls of the Royal Caserta Palace, designed by Vanvitelli.
        The son of Charles, Ferdinand I, had a hunting lodge built for himself on this site. He was a very skillful hunter who disliked the pleasures and luxury of court
        life. It was here that Charles and the young king Ferdinand built a silk factory.
        The complex was transformed into a silk production site and industrial buildings were added, which was quite unique in late 18th-century Europe.
        Architect Francesco Collecini designed these industrial buildings, where noisy looms were installed next to royal apartments and a sitting room became a chapel for the workers.
        A new village was built for workers\' residences, and a large community of silk weavers grew into this industrial town, which in 1789 was deemed the "Real Colonia dei Setaioli" (the Silk Weavers Royal Colony).
        The king had planned to expand it into a true new city, called Ferdinandopoli, but the project was halted by the French invasion.
        In San Leucio the most advanced technologies known in Europe at the time were used throughout the process to obtain the finished products.
        The members of the colony had a privileged status with a modern social security system.
        The revolution of 1799 stopped the complete realization of the Ferdinandopoli, but San Leucio resort had further growth during the French rule from 1806 to 1815.\n
        Source Wikipedia.\n
        Official website:
    </string>
    <string name="san_leucio_website">http://www.comune.caserta.it/pagina698_belvedere-di-san-leucio.html</string>

    <string name="casertavecchia_description">Casertavecchia, a frazione of Caserta, is an Italian medieval village that lies at the foot of
        the Tifatini Mountains located 10 km north-east of the City of Caserta at an altitude of approximately 401 meters. Its name translated from Italian means
        "Old Caserta".\n
         \n
    History\n
        \n
        The origins of Casertavecchia are uncertain, but according to the Benedictine monk, Erchempert, in Ystoriola Langobardorum Beneventi degentium,
        the village was founded in 861 AD. The previous Roman town was called "Casam Irtam" (from the Latin meaning "home village located above").
        The village was initially conquered and ruled by the Lombards. Subsequent Saracen depredations led to the fortified mountain village becoming the Bishopric for
        the province. Under Norman domination, the village began the construction of its cathedral, dedicated to St. Michael the Archangel.
        During this period it was controlled by the Swabian, Riccardo di Lauro (1232–1266), who increased the political power of the town.
        The Aragons conquered the village in 1442 which began its long and gradual decline in importance. Eventually, Casertavecchia would host only the local
        seminary and the Bishop\'s seat. Under the rule of the Bourbons, major construction began taking place in the city of Caserta. By 1842 political rule
        had entirely moved to the great palace in the larger city, with the Casertan diocese finally relocating from Casertavecchia to Caserta.
        On October 1, 1860, in the battle of the Volturna, the Neapolitans made one of their last stands of the battle in front of Caserta Vecchia,
        400–500 Neapolitan soldiers surrendering to Giuseppe Garibaldi in one of the decisive battles of the Second Italian Independence War.\n
        Source Wikipedia.\n
        Official website:
    </string>
    <string name="casertavecchia_website">http://www.casertavecchia.net/</string>


    <string name="pata_pan_description">Fast food \n
Restaurant features:\n Delivery, Takeout, Reservations, Seating, Waitstaff, Parking Available, Highchairs Available, Serves Alcohol, Wine and Beer, Cash Only\n
        Monday 12:30–15, 18:30–02\n
        Tuesday Closed\n
Wednesday- Saturday	12:30–15, 18:30–02\n
Sunday 12:30–15, 18:30–00\n
    Tripadvisor:\n</string>
    <string name="pata_pan_tripadvisor">https://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Restaurant_Review-g194713-d9704600-Reviews-Pata_Pan-Caserta_Province_of_Caserta_Campania.html</string>
    <string name="il_cantuccio_description"> Italian, Mediterranean, Pub\n
Restaurant features:\n  Accepts Visa, Takeout, Reservations, Seating, Waitstaff, Highchairs Available, Wheelchair Accessible, Serves Alcohol, Wine and Beer,
        Accepts American Express, Accepts Mastercard, Digital Payments\n
Open Hours\n
Sunday\n
12:30 - 15:00\n
20:00 - 23:59\n
Monday\n
12:30 - 15:00\n
Tuesday-Friday\n
20:00 - 23:59\n
Saturday\n
20:00 - 01:00\n
Tripadvisor:\n</string>
    <string name="il_cantuccio_tripadvisor">https://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Restaurant_Review-g194713-d8372560-Reviews-Il_Cantuccio_Pub_Beer-Caserta_Province_of_Caserta_Campania.html</string>
    <string name="i_masanielli_description">Pizza, Mediterranean, Vegetarian Friendly, Vegan Options, Gluten Free Options\n
        Restaurant features:  Takeout, Seating, Waitstaff, Television, Highchairs Available, Serves Alcohol\n
Open Hours\n
Tuesday-Sunday\n
12:00 - 00:30\n
Tripadvisor:\n    </string>
    <string name="i_masanielli_tripadvisor">https://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Restaurant_Review-g194713-d3710517-Reviews-Pizzeria_I_Masanielli-Caserta_Province_of_Caserta_Campania.html</string>
    <string name="meburger_description"> Brew Pub, Barbecue, Pub, Vegetarian Friendly\n
Restaurant features  Outdoor Seating, Takeout, Reservations, Seating, Waitstaff, Highchairs Available, Wheelchair Accessible, Serves Alcohol, Free Wifi\n
Open Hours\n
Monday-Sunday\n
19:00 - 15:30\n
Tripadvisor:\n       </string>
    <string name="meburger_tripadvisor">https://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Restaurant_Review-g194713-d8652153-Reviews-Meburger-Caserta_Province_of_Caserta_Campania.html</string>
    <string name="vigna_re_description"> Italian, Seafood\n
Restaurant features:\n
        Reservations, Outdoor Seating, Seating, Waitstaff, Parking Available, Highchairs Available, Wheelchair Accessible, Serves Alcohol, Free Wifi\n
        Monday 13–15:30, 19:30–00\n
        Tuesday Closed\n
Wednesday - Sunday	13–15:30, 19:30–00\n
Tripadvisor:\n         </string>
    <string name="vigna_re_tripadvisor">https://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Restaurant_Review-g2399098-d6158120-Reviews-Moderna_Vineria_Vigna_Re-San_Leucio_Caserta_Province_of_Caserta_Campania.html</string>

    <string name="guggenheim_description"> Bar, European, Pub, Brew Pub\n
Restaurant features:\n
        Takeout, Reservations, Seating, Waitstaff, Parking Available, Television, Wheelchair Accessible, Serves Alcohol, Full Bar\n
Open Hours\n
Monday-Sunday\n
19:00 - 02:30\n
Wednesday closed\n
Tripadvisor:\n</string>
    <string name="guggenheim_tripadvisor">https://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Restaurant_Review-g194713-d7599472-Reviews-Guggenheim-Caserta_Province_of_Caserta_Campania.html</string>

    <string name="san_carlo_description"> International, Italian, Pizza, Seafood, Mediterranean, Soups, Delicatessen, Vegetarian Friendly\n
Restaurant features:\n
        Buffet, Seating, Waitstaff, Parking Available, Street Parking, Free Off-Street Parking, Television, Highchairs Available, Wheelchair Accessible, Serves Alcohol,
        Full Bar, Wine and Beer, Accepts American Express, Accepts Mastercard, Accepts Visa, Free Wifi, Takeout, Reservations\n
Open Hours\n
Tuesday-Sunday\n
12:00 - 14:45\n
19:00 - 23:45\n
Tripadvisor:\n    </string>
    <string name="san_carlo_tripadvisor">https://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Restaurant_Review-g194713-d6592228-Reviews-San_Carlo_Ristorante_Pizzeria-Caserta_Province_of_Caserta_Campania.html</string>
    <string name="i_masanielli_martucci_description"> Italian, Pizza, Vegetarian Friendly, Vegan Options\n
Restaurant features:\n
        Takeout, Reservations, Seating, Waitstaff, Television, Highchairs Available, Serves Alcohol\n
Open Hours\n
Sunday\n
18:30 - 00:00
Monday-Friday\n
12:30 - 15:00\n
18:45 - 00:00\n
Saturday\n
18:30 - 00:00\n
12:00 - 15:00\n
    Tripadvisor:\n </string>
    <string name="i_masanielli_martucci_tripadvisor">https://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Restaurant_Review-g194713-d6839108-Reviews-I_Masanielli_Pizzeria_da_Sasa_Martucci-Caserta_Province_of_Caserta_Campania.html</string>
    <string name="o_tianiello_description"> Italian, Mediterranean, Vegetarian Friendly, Gluten Free Options\n
Restaurant features:\n
        Full Bar, Reservations, Seating, Waitstaff, Wheelchair Accessible, Serves Alcohol, Wine and Beer, Accepts Mastercard, Accepts Visa, Free Wifi\n
Open Hours\n
Sunday\n
12:30 - 15:00\n
Monday-Saturday\n
19:30 - 23:30\n
12:30 - 15:00\n
Tripadvisor:\n     </string>
    <string name="o_tianiello_tripadvisor">https://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Restaurant_Review-g194713-d2649924-Reviews-O_Tianiello-Caserta_Province_of_Caserta_Campania.html</string>
    <string name="hostaria_massa_description"> Italian, Pizza, Seafood, Mediterranean, European, Vegetarian Friendly, Vegan Options, Gluten Free Options\n
Restaurant features:\n
        Parking Available, Valet Parking, Full Bar, Reservations, Outdoor Seating, Private Dining, Seating, Waitstaff, Highchairs Available,
        Wheelchair Accessible, Serves Alcohol, Wine and Beer, Accepts American Express, Accepts Mastercard, Accepts Visa, Free Wifi\n
Open Hours\n
Sunday\n
12:30 - 15:00\n
Monday-Saturday\n
12:30 - 15:00\n
20:00 - 23:00\n
Tripadvisor:\n       </string>
    <string name="hostaria_massa_tripadvisor">https://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Restaurant_Review-g194713-d1732113-Reviews-Antica_Hostaria_Massa-Caserta_Province_of_Caserta_Campania.html</string>


    <string name="hotel_royal_description">
        Internet\n
        Public parking is possible on site (reservation is not needed) and costs EUR 10 per day.\n
        Fitness centre\n
        Restaurant (à la carte)\n
        Breakfast in the room\n
        Bar\n
        Languages spoken: Italian, French, Spanish, English, German\n
        Booking:\n </string>
    <string name="hotel_royal_booking">https://www.booking.com/hotel/it/casertacaserta.en-gb.html?aid=304142;label=gen173nr-1FCAEoggJCAlhYSDNiBW5vcmVmaDqIAQGYARTCAQp3aW5kb3dzIDEwyAEM2AEB6AEB-AELkgIBeagCAw;sid=93e7c7954914c31526ab822e06b6cc4c;dest_id=-114219;dest_type=city;dist=0;group_adults=2;hpos=1;room1=A%2CA;sb_price_type=total;srfid=113d96f2ba03c418ec2837f0cd1c7d6fb0af12b2X1;type=total;ucfs=1;=;lang=en-gb;lang_click=top;cdl=it#availability</string>

    <string name="hotel_vanvitelli_description">
        Internet\n
        Free! Free public parking is possible at a location nearby (reservation is not needed)\n
        Fitness centre\n
        Outdoor pool\n
        Solarium\n
        Restaurant (à la carte)\n
        Breakfast in the room\n
        Bar\n
        Languages spoken: Italian, French, Spanish, English, German\n
        Booking:\n </string>
    <string name="hotel_vanvitelli_booking">https://www.booking.com/hotel/it/grandhotelvanvitelli.en-gb.html?aid=304142;label=gen173nr-1FCAEoggJCAlhYSDNiBW5vcmVmaDqIAQGYARTCAQp3aW5kb3dzIDEwyAEM2AEB6AEB-AELkgIBeagCAw;sid=93e7c7954914c31526ab822e06b6cc4c;dest_id=-114219;dest_type=city;dist=0;group_adults=2;hpos=2;room1=A%2CA;sb_price_type=total;srfid=113d96f2ba03c418ec2837f0cd1c7d6fb0af12b2X2;type=total;ucfs=1;=;lang=en-gb;lang_click=top;cdl=it</string>
    <string name="hotel_cavalieri_description">
        Internet\n
        Public parking is possible at a location nearby (reservation is not needed) and costs EUR 10 per day.\n
        Hot tub/jacuzzi\n
        Restaurant (à la carte)\n
        Kid meals\n
        Breakfast in the room\n
        Languages spoken: Italian, French, Spanish, English\n
        Booking:\n </string>
    <string name="hotel_cavalieri_booking">https://www.booking.com/hotel/it/h2c-caserta.en-gb.html?aid=304142;label=gen173nr-1FCAEoggJCAlhYSDNiBW5vcmVmaDqIAQGYARTCAQp3aW5kb3dzIDEwyAEM2AEB6AEB-AELkgIBeagCAw;sid=93e7c7954914c31526ab822e06b6cc4c;dest_id=-114219;dest_type=city;dist=0;group_adults=2;hpos=3;room1=A%2CA;sb_price_type=total;srfid=113d96f2ba03c418ec2837f0cd1c7d6fb0af12b2X3;type=total;ucfs=1;=;lang=en-gb;lang_click=top;cdl=it</string>

    <string name="hotel_villa_maria_cristina_description">
        Internet\n
        Free! Free private parking is possible at a location nearby (reservation is not needed)\n
        Outdoor pool (seasonal)\n
        Restaurant (à la carte)\n
        Snack bar\n
        Breakfast in the room\n
        Languages spoken: Italian, French, Spanish, English\n
        Booking:\n </string>
    <string name="hotel_villa_maria_cristina_booking">https://www.booking.com/hotel/it/villa-maria-cristina.en-gb.html?aid=304142;label=gen173nr-1FCAEoggJCAlhYSDNiBW5vcmVmaDqIAQGYARTCAQp3aW5kb3dzIDEwyAEM2AEB6AEB-AELkgIBeagCAw;sid=93e7c7954914c31526ab822e06b6cc4c;dest_id=-114219;dest_type=city;dist=0;group_adults=2;hpos=4;room1=A%2CA;sb_price_type=total;srfid=113d96f2ba03c418ec2837f0cd1c7d6fb0af12b2X4;type=total;ucfs=1;=;lang=en-gb;lang_click=top;cdl=it</string>

    <string name="hotel_bruman_description">
        Internet\n
        Free! Free private parking is possible at a location nearby (reservation is not needed)\n
        Bar\n
        Breakfast in the room\n
        Booking:\n </string>
    <string name="hotel_bruman_booking">https://www.booking.com/hotel/it/bruman.en-gb.html?aid=304142;label=gen173nr-1FCAEoggJCAlhYSDNiBW5vcmVmaDqIAQGYARTCAQp3aW5kb3dzIDEwyAEM2AEB6AEB-AELkgIBeagCAw;sid=93e7c7954914c31526ab822e06b6cc4c;dest_id=-114219;dest_type=city;dist=0;group_adults=2;hpos=5;room1=A%2CA;sb_price_type=total;srfid=113d96f2ba03c418ec2837f0cd1c7d6fb0af12b2X5;type=total;ucfs=1;=;lang=en-gb;lang_click=top;cdl=it</string>

    <string name="hotel_novotel_description">
        Internet\n
        Private parking is possible on site (reservation is not needed) and costs EUR 8 per day\n
        Outdoor pool\n
        Solarium\n
        Fitness centre\n
        Bar\n
        Restaurant (à la carte)\n
        Breakfast in the room\n
        Languages spoken: Italian, French, Spanish, English\n
        Booking:\n </string>
    <string name="hotel_novotel_booking">https://www.booking.com/hotel/it/novotelcasertasud.en-gb.html?aid=304142;label=gen173nr-1FCAEoggJCAlhYSDNiBW5vcmVmaDqIAQGYARTCAQp3aW5kb3dzIDEwyAEM2AEB6AEB-AELkgIBeagCAw;sid=93e7c7954914c31526ab822e06b6cc4c;dest_id=-114219;dest_type=city;dist=0;group_adults=2;hpos=6;room1=A%2CA;sb_price_type=total;srfid=113d96f2ba03c418ec2837f0cd1c7d6fb0af12b2X6;type=total;ucfs=1;=;lang=en-gb;lang_click=top;cdl=it</string>

    <string name="via_mazzini_description">This small street hosts mainly clothes shops, usually expensive but with high quality goods.
    you can also find bars, jewelers and the City Theatre.\n
    Website of the City of Caserta:\n</string>
    <string name="caserta_website">http://www.comune.caserta.it/</string>

    <string name="corso_trieste_description">A long street which starts from Piazza Dante and ends close to the Monuments for the Fallen.
        It hosts many kinds of shops, from food to clothes, electronics, books and a small park.\n
    Website of the City of Caserta:\n</string>

    <string name="via_roma_description">Parallel to Corso Trieste, this street is also well known for shopping. You can find clothes, bars,
        electronics, restaurants and pizza.\n
    Website of the City of Caserta:\n</string>

    <string name="centro_campania_description">Located in the close city of Marcianise, it has a very large area with different buildings.
        You can find shops, restaurants, a supermarket and many other activities. Events are frequent.\n
        A shuttle from Caserta train station is available\n
        Opening hours:\n
        Monday-Sunday\n
        Shopping Gallery:\n
        9:00 - 22:00\n
        Campania Square\n
        9:00 - 24:00\n
        Closed on 1st of January, Easter and the 25th of December\n
        Website:\n</string>
    <string name="centro_campania_website">http://it.club-onlyou.com/Campania</string>

    <string name="outlet_la_reggia_description">Located in Marcianise, very close to A1 exit of Caserta Sud, this fashion outlet offers
        discounts from 30%% to 70%% on many brands. Restaurants, bars and a play ground are also present\n
        A shuttle from Naples is available, from Caserta line CLP 111.\n
        Opening hours:\n
        Monday - Sunday\n
        10.00- 21.00\n
        Closed on 25th of December and 1st of January\n
        Website:\n</string>
    <string name="outlet_la_reggia_website">http://www.mcarthurglen.com/it/la-reggia-designer-outlet/en/</string>

</resources>
